myrealityhomes.com 2004-12-04

# Reality Homes Inc - Privacy Policy

**  
PRIVACY POLICY**

Reality Homes Inc. takes your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather and how we use it. These privacy practices apply to the Web site that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy. 

1\. What personally identifiable information does Reality Homes Inc collect?

Reality Homes Inc.'s primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services.

Reality Homes Inc. collects personally identifiable information when you provide it to us, such as when you subscribe for an e-mail newsletter or fill out an contact form. Several of the services that we offer on our sites, such as our message board, may require registration as a condition of use.

2\. What anonymous information does Reality Homes Inc. collect?

Cookies: Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to us. However, cookies tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information. You do not need to have cookies turned on, although active participation in certain areas of our sites may require cookies. In addition, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected by selecting certain options on your browser.

We use tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including: 

keeping count of return visits to our site.   
accumulating and reporting anonymous, statistical information on Web usage

3\. How does Reality Homes Inc. use the information?

Reality Homes Inc. uses the information we gather for two general purposes:

To enhance the user experience on our sites. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you   
To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling users to participate in polls, and message boards.

4\. How does Reality Homes Inc. share the information?

Reality Homes Inc. will make your personally identifiable information available to other companies or people when:

We have your consent to share the information   
We have engaged companies to work with or on behalf of Reality Homes Inc. to provide a product or service that you have requested.   
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process; or we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, or threaten the rights, property, or safety of Reality Homes Inc., our users, or others 

5\. What are my options?

Users who would rather not provide any of the user data requested by our registration process do not need to register with us. You can still view all of the content and use many of the services offered on our site without registering.

6\. How will I know if the privacy policy is changed?

Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected within this area of our Web site.

Reality Homes, Inc.  
1308 Alexander Avenue East, Building B Fife, WA 98424  
Office: (253) 926-6330  
Email: [info@realityhomesinc.com](mailto:info@realityhomesinc.com)
